Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series V is arranged in 679 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series V. BY-LAWS
  - Sub-Series 204-0. Bylaws
    - Local Lodges No. 1 to 799 inclusive (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Local Lodges No. 800 to 1200 inclusive (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Local Lodges No. 1200 to 2325 inclusive (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Local Lodges-General (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-5. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 5-Waycross Lodge, Waycross, Georgia, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-7. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 7-Denver Lodge, Denver, Colorado, 1954-1959 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-11. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 11-Kingsville Lodge, Kingsville, Texas, 1941-1959 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-16. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 16-Hamlet Lodge, Hamlet, North Carolina, 1956-1957 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-17. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 17-Washington Terminal Lodge, Washington, D.C., 1944-1959 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-19. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 19-Dallas-Texas and Pacific Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1934-1959 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-20. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 20-Union Station Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1923-1959 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-22. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 22-Knoxville Lodge, Knoxville, Tennessee, 1924-1959 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-24. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 24-Lookout Lodge, Chattanooga, Tennessee, 1921-1959 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-25. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 25-Missouri Pacific Sedalia Lodge, Sedalia, Missouri, 1939-1944 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-28. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 28-Houston Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1928-1952 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-30. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 30-Southern California Lodge, Los Angeles, California / Southern Pacific Lodge, Los Angeles, California, 1925-1959 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      1938-59; 1925-38.
  - Sub-Series 204-31. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 31-Pine Bluff Lodge, Pine Bluff, Arkansas, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-32. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 32-Waterville Lodge, Fairfield, Maine, 1944-1945 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-34. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 34-Spokane Lodge, Spokane, Washington, 1923-1959 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-36. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 36-Harmony Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1933-1956 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-39. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 39-Southern Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1923-1944 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-40. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 40-Shreveport, Louisiana (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-41. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 41-Invincible Lodge, Maplewood, Missouri, 1943-1954 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-44. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 44-Frisco Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1924-1959 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-45. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 45-San Joaquin Division, Bakersfield, California, 1929-1959 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-46. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 46-Progress Lodge, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1921-1952 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-51. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 51-Kaw Valley Lodge, Topeka, Kansas, 1934-1952 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-53. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 53-Old Reliable Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1923-1959 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-54. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 54-Crescent City Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1943-1959 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-55. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 55-Louisiana Sunset Lodge, Gretna, Louisiana, 1921-1957 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-57. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 57-Shreveport Lodge, Bossier City, Louisiana, 1958-1959 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-59. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 59-Pelican Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1922-1945 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-60. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 60-Piesa Lodge, Alton, Illinois, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-63. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 63-Western Warehousing Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1942-1943 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-64. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 64-Volunteer Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1943-1944 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-67. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 67-Palestine Lodge, Palestine, Texas, 1944-1959 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-70. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 70-New York City Lodge, New York, New York, 1922-1957 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-71. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 71-General Office Lodge, Dorchester, Massachusetts, 1943-1957 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-73. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 73-Windsor Street Station, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, 1928-1929 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-74. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 74-North Union Lodge, Lynn, Massachusetts, 1925-1959 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-75. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 75-Fort Worth Lodge, Fort Worth, Texas, 1950-1956 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-80. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 80-Central Building Lodge, Long Island City, New York, 1944-1949 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-82. Bylaw
    - Lodge No. 82-Danville, Illinois (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-81. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 81-Bridgeport Lodge, Stratford, Connecticut, 1934-1956 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 204-84. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 84-San Jacinto Lodge, Houston, Texas, 1938-1955 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-85. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 85-Lawrence Lodge, Andover, Massachusetts, 1921-1950 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-88. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 88-Manchester Lodge, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-89. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 89-Tampa Lodge, Tampa, Florida, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-90. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 90-Sunrise Lodge, Jamaica, New York, 1939 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-91. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 91-Centralia Lodge, Centralia, Illinois, 1939-1956 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-92. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 92-Pivot City Lodge, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1952-1959 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-97. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 97-M.K.& T Lodge, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1933-1959 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-96. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 96-Triangle Lodge, Springfield, Ohio, 1927-1954 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-98. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 98-Badger State Lodge, Tanesville, Wisconsin, 1937-1959 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-99. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 99-Minot, North Dakota, 1922-1959 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-100. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 100-Girard Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1922-1956 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-102. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 102-Georgia Lodge, Atlanta, Georgia, 1949-1958 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-104. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 104-Jacksonville Lodge, Jacksonville, Florida, 1922-1959 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-109. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 109-St. Joseph Lodge, St. Joseph, Missouri, 1936-1959 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-116. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 116-Utica Lodge, Utica, New York, 1925-1956 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-118. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 118-Vicksburg Lodge, Vicksburg, Mississippi, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      Dec. 16, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 204-119. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 119-Boston Lodge, Somerville, Massachusetts, 1922-1954 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-120. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 120-Chicago, Illinois, 1943-1951 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-124. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 124-Consolidated Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-126. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 126-Terminal Clerks Lodge, Overland Park, Kansas, 1934-1959 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-127. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 127-Agency Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1958-1959 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 204-129. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 129-Gate City Lodge, Winona, Minnesota, 1924 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-130. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 130-Pioneer Valley Lodge, Springfield, Massachusetts, 1941-1947 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-132. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 132-Clear Lake Lodge, Peoria, Illinois, 1938-1959 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-134. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 134-Ideal Lodge, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1938-1945 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-135. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 135-Charlotte Lodge, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1921 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-136. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 136-Kansas City Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1921-1950 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-137. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 137-Des Moines Local Lodge, Des Moines, Iowa, 1924-1952 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-138. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 138-Fostoria, Ohio, 1936-1959 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-139. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 139-La Crosse Lodge, La Crosse, Wisconsin, 1920-1956 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-141. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 141-Harmony Lodge, Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-143. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 143-Old Colony Lodge, Roslindale, Massachusetts, 1923-1957 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-145. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 145-Cotton Belt Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1943-1957 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-149. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 149-Southwest Lodge, Springfield, Missouri, 1937-1959 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-151. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 151-Nebraska Division Lodge, Grand Island, Nebraska, 1946-1953 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-152. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 152-Portland Lodge, Portland, Maine, 1921-1954 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-156. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 156-M.C. General Office Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1936-1956 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-162. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 162-Dearborn Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1937-1959 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-163. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 163-Baggage Employees Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1939-1952 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-168. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 168-Milwukee Junction Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1938-1951 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-175. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 175-Temple Lodge, Temple, Texas, 1925-1952 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-176. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 176-Yadkin Lodge, Salisbury, North Carolina, 1923-1947 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-177. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 177-Long Island Lodge, Huntington Station, New York, 1937-1943 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-178. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 178-George E. Evans Lodge, Louisville, Kentucky, 1944-1952 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-180. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 180-Golden Rod Lodge, Illmo, Missouri, 1922 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-183. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 183-Commodore Lodge, Decatur, Illinois, 1934-1942 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-186. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 186-Hartford Lodge, Hartford, Connecticut, 1922-1942 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-187. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 187-Marquette Lodge, Marquette, Michigan, 1925-1954 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-195. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 195-Phoebe Snow Lodge, Buffalo, New York / Lodge No. 195, Sunflower Lodge, Wellington, Kansas, 1923-1949 (Box 19, Folder 56)
      1942-49; 1923.
  - Sub-Series 204-198. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 198-Sacramento Lodge, Sacramento, California, 1922-1954 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-200. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 200-Hudson River Lodge, New York, New York, 1952-1959 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-203. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 203-Oswatomie Lodge, Osawatomie, Kansas, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Sub-Series 204-205. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 205-Falls City Lodge, Falls City, Nebraska, 1951-1954 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-206. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 206-Triple Cities Lodge, Binghamton, New York, 1941-1942 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-207. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 207-Cincinnati Union Terminal Lodge, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1934-1959 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-209. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 209-Chicago-Alton Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-211. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 211-Port Huron Lodge, Marysville, Michigan, 1942-1959 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-213. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 213-Iron City Lodge, Ashland, Kentucky / Coal Belt Lodge, Hurst, Illinois, 1923-1959 (Box 19, Folder 65)
      1938-59; 1923.
  - Sub-Series 204-215. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 215-Independence Lodge, New Orleans, Louisiana, 1935-1959 (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-223. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 223-Cheyenne Pioneer Lodge, Cheyenne, Wyoming, 1942-1954 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 204-224. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 224-New Haven Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut, 1926-1950 (Box 19, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-226. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 226-Liberty Lodge, Richmond, California, 1945-1956 (Box 19, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 204-227. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 227-Elm City Lodge, New Haven, Connecticut, 1948-1959 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-228. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 228-Old Hickory Lodge, Nashville, Tennessee, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-240. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 240-San Antonio Lodge, San Antonio, Texas, 1941-1954 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-248. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 248-Feather River Lodge, San Carlos, California, 1949-1953 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 204-250. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 250-Hampton Roads Lodge, Portsmouth, Virginia, 1936-1950 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-251. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 251-Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      Nov. 12, 1953.
  - Sub-Series 204-252. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 252-Onondaga Lodge, Syracuse, New York, 1931-1953 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 204-255. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 255-Accounting Lodge, Utica, New York, 1921-1959 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 204-257. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 257-Union Depot Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 204-258. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 258-Laclede Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1921-1959 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 204-260. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 260-Minneapolis Lodge, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1937-1959 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 204-264. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 264-Cornwallis Lodge, Halifax, Nova Scotia, Canada, 1933-1951 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 204-265. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 265-Allentown Lodge, Catasauqua, Pennsylvania, 1949-1959 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 204-266. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 266-Capital City Lodge, Sacramento, California, 1921-1959 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 204-278. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 278-Monon Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1928-1959 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 204-280. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 280-Sunset Lodge, Lemay, Missouri, 1929-1959 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 204-282. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 282-Andy Reed Lodge, Ludlow, Kentucky, 1934-1950 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 204-283. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 283-Blue Eagle Lodge, St. Louis, Missouri, 1938-1959 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 204-284. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 284-Missouri Pacific Lodge, Kansas City, Kansas, 1921-1956 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 204-286. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 286-Oklahoma City Lodge, Norman, Oklahoma, 1921-1959 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 204-287. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 287-Viking Lodge, St. John's, Newfoundland, Canada, 1939-1950 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 204-288. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 288-Little Rock Lodge, Little Rock, Arkansas, 1926-1959 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 204-289. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 289-Banner Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1926-1956 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 204-293. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 293-Red Stick Lodge, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1953-1959 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 204-295. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 295-Lakeport Lodge, Kingston, Ontario, Canada, 1938-1948 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 204-296. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 296-Flint Lodge, Clio, Michigan, 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 204-297. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 297-Dixie Lodge, Memphis, Tennessee, 1951-1959 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 204-299. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 299-Gem City Lodge, Dayton, Ohio, 1925 (Box 20, Folder 28)
      1925 July 3
  - Sub-Series 204-300. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 300-Sioux Falls Lodge, Sioux Falls, South Dakota, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 204-302. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 302-Norfolk Lodge, Norfolk, Virginia, 1942-1956 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 204-303. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 303-Newport, Kentucky, 1942 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 204-304. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 304-Terminal Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1946-1951 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 204-307. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 307-Dallas Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1937-1955 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 204-308. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 308-We-Will Lodge, Huntington, West Virginia, 1935-1959 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 204-315. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 315-White Oak Lodge, Hinton, West Virginia, 1935-1962 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 204-316. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 316-Pass City Lodge, El Paso, Texas, 1946-1954 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 204-320. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 320-General Office Lodge, Richmond, Virginia, 1935-1954 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Sub-Series 204-321. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 321-Milwaukee Lodge, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 1933-1959 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Sub-Series 204-330. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 330-San Joaquin Lodge, Stockton, California, 1923-1947 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Sub-Series 204-331. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 331-Hoboken Lodge, West Keansburg, New Jersey, 1923-1959 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Sub-Series 204-333. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 333-Harmony Lodge, Chicago, Illinois, 1921-1922 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Sub-Series 204-335. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 335-Streamliner Lodge, Omaha, Nebraska, 1937-1958 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Sub-Series 204-340. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 340-Willmar Lodge, Willmar, Minnesota, 1922 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Sub-Series 204-341. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 341-Big Four Lodge, Columbus, Ohio, 1925-1951 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Sub-Series 204-342. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 342-Emancipation Lodge, River Grove, Illinois, 1925-1954 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Sub-Series 204-344. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 344-Red Caps Lodge, Grandview, Missouri, 1939-1957 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Sub-Series 204-345. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 345-South Shore Lodge, Munster, Indiana, 1936-1959 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Sub-Series 204-346. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 346-Gander Lodge, Villa Park, Illinois, 1953-1959 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Sub-Series 204-349. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 349-Lechmere Lodge, Marblehead, Massachusetts, 1944-1955 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Sub-Series 204-350. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 350-General Office Lodge, Detroit, Michigan, 1939-1940 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Sub-Series 204-352. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 352-Freight Handlers Lodge, Des Plaines, Illinois, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Sub-Series 204-353. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 353-Stone Mountain Lodge, College Park, Georgia, 1943-1953 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Sub-Series 204-354. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 354-Grand Trunk Lodge, Allen Park, Michigan, 1942-1959 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Sub-Series 204-359. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 359-Roosevelt Lodge, Ashland, Kentucky, 1935-1957 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Sub-Series 204-360. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 360-Mount Vernon Lodge, Alexandria, Virginia, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Sub-Series 204-362. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 362-Tidewater Lodge, Hampton, Virginia, 1935-1951 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Sub-Series 204-364. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 364-Gopher Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1939-1956 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Sub-Series 204-366. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 366-Terre Haute Lodge, Terre Haute, Indiana, 1929-1959 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Sub-Series 204-369. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 369-Boone Lodge, Boone, Iowa, 1921-1959 (Box 20, Folder 59)
      1921-1959.
  - Sub-Series 204-370. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 370-C. ST. P.M. & O. Lodge, St. Paul, Minnesota, 1934-1959 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Sub-Series 204-371. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 371-Erie Lodge, Erie, Pennsylvania, 1945-1951 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Sub-Series 204-373. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 373-Ore Handlers Lodge, Ashland, Wisconsin, 1922-1959 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - Sub-Series 204-374. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 374-Maine Central General Office Lodge, Portland, Maine, 1926-1959 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Sub-Series 204-382. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 382-Missouri Lodge, Mandan, North Dakota, 1959 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Sub-Series 204-383. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 383-Trinity Lodge, Dallas, Texas, 1953-1959 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Sub-Series 204-384. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 384-Liberty City Lodge, West Branch, Iowa, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Sub-Series 204-390. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 390-Philadelphia Lodge, Hatboro, Pennsylvania, 1939-1959 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Sub-Series 204-391. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 391-Kansas City Lodge, Kansas City, Missouri, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Sub-Series 204-392. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 392-Seattle Lodge, Seattle, Washington, 1923-1950 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Sub-Series 204-393. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 393-Arkansas Valley Lodge, Uniontown, Arkansas, 1928-1933 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Sub-Series 204-395. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 395-Tayhawk Lodge, Salina, Kansas, 1942-1958 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Sub-Series 204-397. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 397-Black Hawk Lodge, Waterloo, Iowa, 1923-1959 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Sub-Series 204-404. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 404-Manhattan Lodge, Brooklyn, New York, 1922-1932 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Sub-Series 204-408. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 408-Twin City Lodge, Fort William, Ontario, Canada, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Sub-Series 204-409. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 409-Connellsville Lodge, Connellsville, Pennsylvania, 1941-1959 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Sub-Series 204-410. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 410-Jersey City Lodge, Jersey City, New Jersey, 1939-1949 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Sub-Series 204-411. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 411-Freight Handlers Lodge, Maple Heights, Ohio, 1949-1959 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Sub-Series 204-415. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 415-Badger Lodge, Superior, Wisconsin, 1948-1949 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Sub-Series 204-416. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 416-South Union Lodge, Middlesboro, Massachusetts, 1922-1955 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 204-417. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 417-Tri-Cities Lodge, Barstock, Illinois, 1925-1959 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 204-418. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 418-Fort Arthur Lodge, Fort Arthur, Ontario, Canada, 1953 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 204-419. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 419-Pacific Coast Lodge, Portland, Oregon, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      Feb. 28, 1957.
  - Sub-Series 204-421. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 421-Square Deal Lodge, Harrisburg, Pennsylvania, 1937-1958 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 204-425. Bylaws
    - Lodge No. 425-Recovery Lodge, Queens Village, New York, 1953-1959 (Box 21, Folder 6)